[Episode 22]
The scenery here is beautiful,
surrounded by clouds and mist.
Looking up from the bottom of the valley,
it's like a fairyland.
The scenery in this painting looks similar.
Luo, do you know a flower--
Luo.
I see many flowers in this courtyard.
May I ask what they are used for?
Tomorrow is the Flower Festival here.
I'm busy preparing flower cakes
for the festival.
I'll leave you all to rest and talk.
If you need anything, just let me know.
Miss Meng,
I was about to ask about the Fuqing herb.
- Why did you...
- We just got here.
Bringing it up rashly might alert the enemy.
Miss Meng.
Luo is kind-hearted and simple.
She saved me when I got bitten
by a venomous snake.
She lived here with her brother.
The local people almost live in isolation.
They rarely interact with outsiders.
Just in case.
Let's check out the situation on our own.
Yin Qing, you're familiar
with the mountain terrain.
You'll arrange our operation.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
The local terrain is complex.
There are snakes, insects, and rats.
For safety's sake,
I suggest men and women pair up to search.
I will go with Zhi Li.
Relax.
Is Zhi Li your sister or mine?
Then I'll reluctantly go with Miss Yan.
You've beaten me to it.
Who exactly is reluctant? Make it clear.
Just a slip of the tongue.
I mean, it's my honor to protect Miss Yan.
That's more like it.
I'll go with Miss Meng--
You're too weak to protect Miss Meng.
I'll go with her tomorrow.
No matter what you find,
you must return before dark.
- What about me?
- Huang.
You have much to do here.
Huang, talk more with Luo
to build some rapport.
Don't talk nonsense.
Huang, I mean,
you should build a friendship with Luo
to learn about the local customs here.
What are you thinking?
Huang, are you thinking of having a thing--
No, I'm not.
What a beautiful land!
I've seen the gorgeous scenery here
and the wildness in Shazhou.
Amidst the beautiful land,
there are many sceneries
I have never seen before.
How time flies.
I've been away from Shazhou for a long time.
Were you born in Shazhou,
or brought to Shazhou by traffickers?
I don't remember.
As long as I can remember,
I have lived in Shazhou.
What about your parents?
Do you still remember them?
I can't remember anything before that.
I feel like
Your Majesty has been asking
about my past recently.
It seems like you're investigating me.
Can't I be curious about you?
Your Majesty, aren't you clear about my past?
I have seen the darkness,
so I must break it down completely.
You take a break here.
I'll go find something to eat.
Look, I got you some fresh wild fruit.
You can eat them.
Is it good?
So sweet.
Want one?
No, thanks.
It's so cold.
I'll add some more firewood.
What's wrong with you?
I feel hot.
But it's cold. Don't catch a cold.
Your Majesty,
it's my first time seeing you up close.
You're not acting like yourself.
What's wrong?
What's going on?
You try it.
Do not eat it.
There's something wrong with this fruit.
Do you still remember who you are?
Look, do you know who I am?
Meng Ting Hui.
A subject who seduces the ruler
will be sentenced to death.
If you take one more step,
we will both be doomed beyond redemption.
A ruler who dotes on a subject
deserves to write a self-reproach edict.
Your Majesty, are you afraid?
I have never been afraid.
Me neither.
Miss Meng.
Miss Shen, you're back.
Come and sit.
Zhi Li.
- Give it to me.
- Be careful. It's hot.
Thanks.
- Zhi Li.
- Thanks.
Mr. Shen, you're back too. Come and sit.
I can't believe you.
You have such a bad sense of direction.
We haven't found anything.
My legs feel so tired.
You've been complaining about being tired,
so we kept resting, right?
Otherwise, we would have long arrived.
Master, you're back.
Meng.
You're back.
What's wrong with you?
Why is your face so red?
I picked plenty of fresh wild fruit
to quench your thirst.
- Here you go.
- Well...
Fu Zhi.
Don't eat that.
Why not?
This is the Hehuan fruit.
Couples eat it to have a child.
The wild fruits all look similar.
Master, how did you know it?
I have good news for you.
I've found the Fuqing herb.
Why are you only saying it now?
Well...
Alright, shut up.
Luo.
Do you know this Fuqing herb?
Fuqing herb?
In our valley, we call it Jinqian herb.
Every household grows it deep in the valley.
Luo.
We need to tell you something.
The herbalist is surnamed Lv.
He said Jinqian herbs are rare and precious.
That's why we started growing it
in large quantities.
We just want to make a living here
by exchanging herbs
for money to meet our daily needs.
We didn't expect
that they would use Jinqian herbs
to do so many evil things.
Luo, don't be nervous.
We tell you frankly
because we believe you were used by bad guys.
Seven days ago, my brother
was responsible for delivering the herbs.
I originally thought he went hunting.
But...
Could he have...
Luo, don't worry.
We are here to find the one behind this
and capture the entire criminal gang.
Tomorrow, we will deliver the herbs
to go into the belly of the beast.
I'm willing to help deal with those bad guys.
Originally, herbs were only delivered
at the beginning of each month.
But we just received news
that the herbalist
urgently wants our whole stock.
It must be delivered early tomorrow morning.
Luo, come and help prepare the flowers!
Luo.
This matter is of great importance.
Do not tell anyone else about it.
I understand, Miss Meng.
I know what to do.
You guys talk here.
I'll go deal with the things out there.
Ling Yun Fei and his men
are very likely hiding
in their pill-making place.
Your Majesty, I have received news.
Since the local terrain is complex,
the main force of the Divine Guards
has been blocked on the way here.
They will arrive at noon tomorrow.
But the herbalist will trade
early tomorrow morning.
If we wait for the army,
we will surely miss the opportunity.
Luo's brother and other missing locals
are very likely to become hostages.
The longer they're gone,
the more danger they are in.
The situation has changed.
Please make a decision, Your Majesty.
Di Nian, you leave the valley tonight.
At all costs,
lead the Divine Guards to rush here.
Zhi Shu.
You stay here with Zhi Li and Fu Zhi
to protect the locals
and meet up with the Divine Guard.
Yes, Your Majesty.
What about Meng?
The plan remains unchanged,
but the way to follow it needs to change.
Tomorrow, we will disguise ourselves
as locals delivering herbs
and infiltrate
to buy time for Di Nian
and the Divine Guards.
I'm going with Miss Meng.
Tomorrow, we must capture Ling Yun Fei
and destroy the Eternity Pills.
[Blood Moon Society]
Ying Gua and Meng Ting Hui
have located Wangxian Valley.
Tomorrow,
they'll sneak in the Poisoned People's Mound.
Mr. Shangguan actually let them investigate.
Now a lot of Eternity Pills
have been produced.
If the Poisoned People's Mound is destroyed--
That's actually what Mr. Shangguan wants.
Mr. Shangguan originally intended
to make money through the Eternity Pills.
But Ling Yun Fei is a mad dog.
He'll stop at nothing to kill Meng Ting Hui.
He even dared to attack Mr. Shangguan.
He has long been out of control.
Mr. Shangguan has ordered the pill-makers
to transfer in batches.
The Poisoned People's Mound
and Ling Yun Fei have been abandoned.
It's kind of a gift to Meng Ting Hui.
It's to invite the enemy into the trap.
Mr. Shangguan wants to set them up.
He will make Ying Gua
and Ling Yun Fei kill each other.
Whether Ling Yun Fei lives or dies
doesn't matter.
But Ying Gua must die
in the Poisoned People's Mound.
Then the world will only think
that Ling Yun Fei killed the emperor.
Without a ruler,
this beautiful land
will eventually belong to Zhongwan.
Kill Ying Gua!
Go on.
Feed them all pills.
Yes.
Master, a letter from Lord Gu.
- Read it.
- Meng Ting Hui has left the capital.
Stop making Eternity Pills. Don't...
Go on!
Don't go crazy and implicate me.
Who is he to tell me what to do?
I won't listen to him!
Tell those pill-makers
to make Eternity Pills faster.
This time, I'll make Meng Ting Hui
taste the Eternity Pill
and disturb the peace of the capital.
Master.
Our gang has been raided.
And we retreated here.
We've lost more than half of our men.
It's not advisable
to fight head-on right now.
- Where there is life, there is hope.
- What about Ru Yan's death?
What about Lv Er's death?
If you're afraid of death, get lost now.
Master, don't get me wrong.
I've been working with you
for over ten years.
When have I ever said I was afraid?
I will never betray you, Master.
All these years,
you have risked your life for me.
You treat me better than my own brother.
But Meng Ting Hui killed our beloved ones.
If we don't avenge their deaths,
what's the point of living in this world?
Master.
I know how you suffer after Ru Yan died.
I also want to avenge my brother's death.
Since you have decided,
I'll be with you, alive or dead.
Good brother.
But Master,
Lord Gu said that Meng Ting Hui
and others are not in the capital.
Could they have found Wangxian Valley?
These Eternity Pills are almost complete.
Those locals are a burden.
When the last batch of herbs is delivered,
you take our men
to slaughter the valley once and for all.
Every year at the Flower Festival,
we exchange flowers to convey our feelings.
This bouquet is for you.
May you be safe and well.
Thank you, Luo.
Then we wish you and other locals
peace and safety year after year.
Thanks.
Huang, why are you smiling?
Huang.
Thankfully, Luo took care of you
when you were injured.
Shouldn't you give a bouquet
to express your gratitude?
Yes, Huang Bo, we're leaving tomorrow.
Come on.
Luo.
I owe you big time.
Huang.
Are you going
to become sworn siblings with Luo?
Nian, look, I owe you big time.
Thanks.
Miss.
Will you swing with us?
Take it. Let's go.
Xiao Yue,
I'll use this peach wood as a witness.
I wish to enjoy the flowers with you
and live an ordinary life together.
I hope we're together forever.
Me too.
Why did he give the peach wood?
This is a tradition here.
Peach wood is used to express love.
Zhi Li.
The locals say that during the festival,
they give flowers as blessings.
I'm about to leave the valley.
So I'm giving you this.
Nian, with these flowers,
I wish you would find a girl you like.
Then I won't have to worry about you anymore.
This is a local specialty.
It's not available in the capital.
Luo, what's wrong?
Every year at the Flower Festival,
my brother always
makes my favorite flower cakes.
If only my brother were here.
That is beautiful.
Do you want to learn?
Luo.
Look.
Is it not pretty?
I think it's very pretty.
This is the most special flower wreath
I've ever seen.
Looks good?
Sure.
The festival is almost over,
but you haven't given out your bouquet yet.
It's hard to find the right one.
I need to choose a suitable place
to prove my sincerity.
So, you have your eye on my swing?
I'll let you have it.
I've looked around,
but none of the girls here
are as pretty as you.
Shen Zhi Shu.
How many girls have you sweet-talked?
Yes.
I used to be a playboy.
I thought I was happy.
But since I met you,
I've realized what fear is.
What do you fear?
I fear you frown.
I fear you turn away.
I'm more afraid...
I'm more afraid you won't believe
that I have eyes only for you.
Perhaps at this moment, you like me.
But how long will you like me?
So many noble ladies in the capital like you.
Are you really willing to give them all up?
I promise you.
If I flirt with any woman,
you can just leave me.
Can you give me a chance to prove my love?
How much do they cost?
You don't have to buy them.
What I fear most is that you don't know
they cost me several years of salary.
If you don't, how can I prove my sincerity?
I know.
You're afraid that you'll hinder my career.
But how could I not know
how you feel about me?
And how could you not know
how I feel about you?
They fit quite well.
I knew the right size the first time we met.
Don't be silly.
Does it still hurt?
Sure.
This way, I'll keep it in mind forever.
The Flower Festival is vibrant out there.
Why don't you go join them?
I feel mixed emotions
when I see those local people.
They are so simple and honest.
They originally wanted
to use the Fuqing herbs to earn money.
But they were used by the Huxiao Gang,
helping them make the Eternity Pills.
It's not the sword that kills,
but the person who wields it.
The Fuqing herb is actually not scary.
What's scary are people
with ulterior motives.
Go forward along this path for ten li.
That's where we trade herbs
with the herbalist.
The mountain road is rugged.
We need to travel through the night.
Please help me find my brother.
Luo, don't worry.
We will definitely find a way
to find your brother.
Don't worry.
Your leg injury hasn't healed yet.
You must be careful.
This is the sachet I embroidered.
My brother has one too.
I hope both of you can stay safe.
Luo.
I don't have anything to give you.
When I come back,
I'll make a beautiful wreath for you.
I'll wait for you.
It's getting late. We should set off.
Hey, sirs.
Here are the four boxes of Fuqing herbs.
Please take a look.
I've been watching you two for a while.
Haven't seen you before.
Well, here is the thing.
Do you want to die?
Sir, please calm down.
It's his first time delivering herbs,
and he doesn't know the rules.
The herbs are all here. Well...
- Get lost!
- Sure.
May you make a fortune.
Quick, send these herbs to the warehouse.
Nothing found.
Have they already been sent to the capital?
It seems they have already noticed.
Miss Meng.
Are you looking for the Eternity Pills?
I've brought them for you.
Today we will destroy your den
and take you back to the capital for trial.
You're in my territory.
How dare you talk big!
I've ordered the Divine Guards
to surround this place.
I won't let you use the Eternity Pills
to wreak havoc in the capital.
Here comes the emperor.
But here's the thing, my place is lawless.
See?
They have been fed plenty of Eternity Pills.
They have long turned
from pill users into poison carriers.
If they appear on the streets of the capital,
what will happen?
The entire capital will become my purgatory.
All the people will die with you.
This is the sachet I embroidered.
My brother has one too.
That's Luo's brother.
It's been so long.
I wonder if things are going well for Meng.
I heard that honey water
helps relieve fatigue and sleep.
I specially made it with warm water,
not too hot or too cold.
Try it.
Shen Zhi Shu, you're cheating!
Now that's cheating.
Zhi Shu.
You two...
It's just as you see.
We are together.
I expected you two would end up together.
But you are now inseparable
and lovey-dovey.
It really surprises me.
If you're envious, go find one yourself.
Is it sweet?
Yes.
Mr. Shen, Miss Shen.
Luo.
It's bad.
I just saw some strangers outside the valley.
They look like those Fuqing herb buyers.
Luo, you don't know martial arts.
Is there a safe hiding place in the valley?
Yes, deep in the valley,
there is an abandoned watchtower.
That's where the local people usually rest.
That's a good hiding place.
You go hide there quickly.
I will notify the locals
to go there immediately.
I'll go with you.
Don't worry. I'll meet up with you soon.
Zhi Shu, be careful.
Remember to drink it.
Come on!
Move!
- Come on!
- Move fast!
Kneel!
Don't hit my sister.
Master Ling has ordered not to harm children.
Please, sir, spare our lives.
We are just farmers.
Farmers?
Yes.
That's perfect.
Use your blood to fertilize the land.
Niu!
Stop!
Mr. Shen.
You are quite smart.
You actually found us.
You don't even spare the weaklings.
You are worse than beasts.
They are all worthless people.
What's the big deal?
Everyone here must die,
including you.
Kill them all!
Chase them!
Chase!
Everyone, get up.
You are safe now.
Thank you, Mr. Shen.
Go back quickly. Go back.
Your Majesty.
We were blocked by their guards for a while,
so we're late.
It's fine.
They've moved out the Eternity Pills.
Yin Qing, go search and see
if there are any Eternity Pills left here.
Destroy them all.
Huang Bo,
come with me to contain Ling Yun Fei.
Yes.
I can't believe you're still alive.
Ling Yun Fei.
You have harmed my people
and wreaked havoc on the country.
That's a heinous crime.
Today, you'll die!
Kill them!
Your Majesty, be careful!